100layercake.com 2017-12-02

# Privacy Policy & Terms of Use - 100 Layer Cake

## Privacy Policy & Terms of Service

100 Layer Cake is committed to protecting your privacy and using technology that gives you the safest andmost powerful online experience. We promise to work hard to earn and keep your trust, and therefore we will never rent or sell your personally identifiable information to third party services for marketing purposes or share your contact information with another user without your consent.

By using the 100 Layer Cake website, you consent to the data practices described in this Policy. We will post notices of all changes that materially affect the way in which your personally identifiable information may be used or shared in updates to our Privacy Policy. If you continue to use 100 Layer Cake's website and services after these notices of changes have been posted to the site, you hereby provide your consent to the changed practices.

### Third Party ad servers or ad networks

Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and for reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, 100layercake.com/blog has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

### Collection and use of Personal Information

When visiting 100layercake.com and 100layercake.com/blog, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

You may visit 100layercake.com and 100layercake.com/blog without revealing any personal information, however we need some personal information when you decide to list an item for sale, to post a vendor request, to big on a vendor request, to post your portfolio or when you decide to comment on a blog post. For ex. when you want to comment on a blog post, we need your email address in order to approve all comments.

By accessing our services and voluntarily providing us with the requested personal information, you consent to the collection and use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

### Sharing of personal information in the Marketplace

When making a purchase or listing an item for sale on 100layercake.com, please be aware that 100 Layer Cake is not responsible for any transactions you choose to engage in once you leave our site. We do not process any transactions for our marketplace through our site. These are "on your honor" agreements that you are entering into with a third party, not related in any way to 100 Layer Cake. If you are suspicious of a buyer or seller, use the same judgement you would when purchasing anything online from an anonymous source. Never give your bank account number or any other information that could be used in a malicious way.

Likewise, when you create or respond to a vendor request, 100 Layer Cake is in no way responsible for the ultimate success or failure of these jobs. Any agreement you enter into with a vendor or client should be at your own discretion. 100 Layer Cake is a venue for clients and vendors to connect, but ultimately does not enforce any contracts created between the two parties.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

We may share some of your personal information to third party partners if this is needed in order to provide you services or products requested by you. We share personal information only if third party's Privacy Policies are consistent with ours or if they agree to abide by our policies with respect to personal information.

We may otherwise disclose your personal information when:

  * You give us your express consent for a specified purpose
  * We need to respond to subpoenas, court orders or such other legal process
  * We need to protect the personal safety of the users of our website or defend our rights or property
  * We find that your actions on our websites violate our Terms of Use document or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services

### Links to third party Websites

We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

### Consent

If you do not consent to the collection, use or disclosure of your personal information , as this Privacy Policy outlines, please do not provide us any personal information. Providing personal information to us means that you agree to our Privacy Policy and Terms of Use.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy and Terms of Service

We may at any time, without notice to you, amend this policy. Please review this policy periodically. Your continued use of 100 Layer Cake websites after any such amendments signifies your acceptance of our current privacy policy and terms of service.
